录制，翻译，特效：布尔
字体：思源宋体 SemiBold
歌曲名称: A Quick Break
四重唱组合名:
'Shoptimus Prime
It's nice to rest your eyes
休息一下眼睛好
And maybe go outside
也许出去溜达溜达
Grab a book and get some air,
带上书 透透气
So what are you waiting for?
所以你还在等什么
Bum bum bum bum
Why not take a quick break?
为何不快快休息一下
Tune the radio
调调收音机
There's chores to do,
还有杂活得做
There's leaves to rake,
落叶该耙一耙了
Strum the old banjo
奏起老班卓琴
You can practice your lindy hop
你可以练练林迪舞步
Bum bum bum bum
And maybe later sing with your barbershop
或者待会儿来一曲理发店四重唱
Why not take a little quick break,
为何不快快休息一下
And come back for more?
然后回来继续玩
Then come back for more?
Please come back for more!
还请你回来继续玩